Guide to the Lewis Perry Curtis Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Sullivan Family, 1916-1980; Series III; 3.3 linear feet (8 boxes)
  - Cannon, Beekman Cox, 1938-1976, undated (Box 18, Folder 562)
  - Cannon, Margaret, 1946-1947, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 563)
  - Carden, Constance Sullivan(*), 1916-1932 (Box 18, Folder 564-568)
  - Carden, Constance Sullivan, 1932-1979, undated (Box 19, Folder 569-578)
  - Carden, Constance Sullivan: concert program, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 579)
  - Carden, George A., Jr., 1979 (Box 19, Folder 580)
  - Carden, Timothy, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 580)
  - Carden, William V., 1978 (Box 19, Folder 580)
  - Castagnet, Annette, 1944-1949 (Box 19, Folder 581)
  - Chrystie, Frances N.(*), 1924-1978, undated (Box 19, Folder 582)
  - Clark, Charlotte L., 1954-1964 (Box 19, Folder 583)
  - Clerf, Eugenie, 1931-1933 (Box 19, Folder 584)
  - Coffin, Henry L., 1929 (Box 19, Folder 585)
  - Cooper, James Wayne, 1943-1976 (Box 19, Folder 586)
  - Cooper, Louise Field(*), 1931-1978 (Box 19, Folder 587-588)
  - Crittenden, Lorraine, 1942-1943 (Box 19, Folder 589)
  - Crosby, Sarah(*), 1948-1972, undated (Box 19, Folder 590)
  - Crosby, Sumner M., 1978 (Box 19, Folder 590)
  - Curtis, Alice Beardsley(*), 1942-1947 (Box 19, Folder 591)
  - Curtis, Alison Willis-Bund(*), 1961-1980, undated (Box 19, Folder 592-593)
  - Curtis, Anne, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 594)
  - Curtis, Elizabeth Steele, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 595)
  - Curtis, Elizabeth MacDonald, 1929-1959 (Box 19, Folder 596)
  - Curtis, Jeanet Sullivan(*), 1926-1975, undated (Box 20, Folder 597-602)
  - Curtis, Lewis Perry (1932-), 1972-1978 (Box 20, Folder 603)
  - Curtis, Louisa Wells(*), 1932-1939 (Box 20, Folder 604)
  - Curtis, Michael Charles, 1973,1975, n d. (Box 20, Folder 605)
  - Curtis, Michael Ellinwood, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 606)
  - Curtis, Pelham, 1928 (Box 20, Folder 607)
  - Curtis, Sarah, 1978, undated (Box 20, Folder 608)
  - Curtiss, Joseph Toy, 1929-1978 (Box 20, Folder 609)
  - D, 1938-1972 (Box 20, Folder 610)
  - Debay, Jeannine, 1921-1935 (Box 20, Folder 611)
  - Desmond, Alice Curtis(*), 1941-1979, undated (Box 20, Folder 612)
  - Donaldson, Virginia, 1946-1964 (Box 20, Folder 613)
  - Dunham, William Huse, Jr., 1970-1974 (Box 20, Folder 614)
  - E, 1929-1961 (Box 20, Folder 615)
  - Egerer, Joel W., 1956-1962, undated (Box 20, Folder 616)
  - d'Entreves, Comte Alèssandro, 1959-1980 (Box 20, Folder 617)
  - F, 1940-1973, undated (Box 20, Folder 618)
  - Fischer, Ann(*), 1954-1979 (Box 20, Folder 619)
  - French, Margeret S., 1931-1947, undated (Box 20, Folder 620)
  - French, Robert Dudley, 1932-1947 (Box 20, Folder 621)
  - Frost, Elizabeth, 1938, 1940, undated (Box 20, Folder 622)
  - G, 1929-1978, undated (Box 20, Folder 623)
  - Gardiner, Alice, 1947-1955 (Box 20, Folder 624)
  - Gardiner, Emily(*), 1929-1979, undated (Box 20, Folder 625)
  - Geffcken, Alwine(*), 1929-1950 (Box 20, Folder 626)
  - Geffcken, Walter, 1928-1950 (Box 20, Folder 627)
  - Given, Dorothy(*), 1942-1952 (Box 20, Folder 628)
  - Glasgow, Mary C.(*), 1954-1979 (Box 21, Folder 629)
  - Griswold, A. Whitney, 1942-1944 (Box 21, Folder 630)
  - Griswold, Mary, 1931-1939, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 631)
  - Groesbeck, Amy, 1942-1943 (Box 21, Folder 632)
  - H, 1922-1980, undated (Box 21, Folder 633)
  - Haight, Mary, 1954-1976, undated (Box 21, Folder 634)
  - Hardigg, Alice Hendrick(*), 1945-1978 (Box 21, Folder 635)
  - Hardigg, James Sutton, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 636)
  - Hardigg, Jeanet Ellinwood, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 636)
  - Hardigg, Viva, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 636)
  - Hendrick, Arthur Pomeroy, 1945-1979 (Box 21, Folder 637)
  - Hendrick, Elinor Sullivan(*), 1921-1980, undated (Box 21, Folder 638-643)
  - Hendrick, Ellwood, 1927-1928 (Box 21, Folder 644)
  - Hendrick, James Pomeroy(*), 1931-1979 (Box 21, Folder 645)
  - Hendrick, Josephine Pomeroy(*), 1929-1950 (Box 21, Folder 646)
  - Hendrick, Robert E. P., 1951-1978 (Box 21, Folder 647)
  - Henning, Alison P.(*), 1970-1980, undated (Box 21, Folder 648)
  - Hetzel, Margaret, 1939-1940 (Box 21, Folder 649)
  - Hewitt, Norman S., 1936, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 650)
  - Hewitt, Ruth, 1932-1944 (Box 21, Folder 651)
  - Hilles, Frederick W.(*), 1924-1974 (Box 21, Folder 652)
  - Hogan, Caroline C.(*), 1936-1972, undated (Box 21, Folder 653)
  - Hogan, Charles Beecher, 1931-1957 (Box 21, Folder 654)
  - J, 1929-1949, undated (Box 21, Folder 655)
  - Jackson, Rose H.(*), 1939-1972, undated (Box 21, Folder 656)
  - K, 1954-1978 (Box 22, Folder 657)
  - Keble, Edward, 1926-1928 (Box 22, Folder 658)
  - Kent, Sherman, 1936-1978 (Box 22, Folder 659)
  - Kingsley, Bessie, 1924-1929, undated (Box 22, Folder 660)
  - Kitson, Ernest(*), 1925-1956, undated (Box 22, Folder 661)
  - Kopper, Florine D., 1932-1958 (Box 22, Folder 662)
  - L, 1929-1979, undated (Box 22, Folder 663)
  - LaFarge, Hester, 1932, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 664)
  - LaFarge, Mabel, 1932, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 664)
  - Lascelles, Alice, 1956-1977 (Box 22, Folder 665)
  - Lascelles, Leila(*), 1954-1973, undated (Box 22, Folder 666)
  - Leake, Bertha, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 667)
  - Lohmann, Helen A.(*), 1940-1958 (Box 22, Folder 668)
  - Lowndes, Marion Smith(*), 1924-1979 (Box 22, Folder 669)
  - Mac, 1932-1977 (Box 22, Folder 670)
  - M, 1929-1979 (Box 22, Folder 671)
  - McAllister, Nancy, 1972-1979 (Box 22, Folder 672)
  - McDill, John Harcourt, 1937-1977 (Box 22, Folder 673)
  - McDill, Julia Lee(*), 1924-1980, undated (Box 22, Folder 674-676)
  - McIntyre, Field, 1954-1976, undated (Box 22, Folder 677)
  - McIntyre, Mithra, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 678)
  - MacKenty, Bunny Walker(*), 1930-1977, undated (Box 22, Folder 679-681)
  - Mason Mannheim, Madeline(*), 1921-1932 (Box 22, Folder 682)
  - Maurer, Lisbet Goffcken, 1928-1932 (Box 22, Folder 683)
  - Maxwell, Carrie, 1954, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 684)
  - Mercier, Jeannot, 1945-1946 (Box 22, Folder 685)
  - Miani, Beatrice Dampierre, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 686)
  - Monkman, Julia, 1977-1979 (Box 22, Folder 687)
  - Monkman, Kenneth, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 688)
  - Morgan, Agnes, 1929-1979 (Box 22, Folder 689)
  - Mosle, Harold K.(*), 1921 (Box 22, Folder 690)
  - Muller, Ida, 1941-1943 (Box 22, Folder 691)
  - Murdoch, R. Alan, 1977-1978, undated (Box 22, Folder 692)
  - Murdock, Rosemary, 1974, undated (Box 22, Folder 693)
  - N., 1959-1977 (Box 22, Folder 694)
  - Notestein, Ada Comstock(*), 1943-1965, undated (Box 22, Folder 695)
  - Notestein, Wallace, 1949-1954 (Box 22, Folder 696)
  - O, 1946-1972 (Box 23, Folder 697)
  - Owen, Louise H., 1937-1939, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 698)
  - P, 1924-1978, undated (Box 23, Folder 699)
  - Padnos, Michael, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 700)
  - Padnos, Nancy Curtis, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 701)
  - Page, Mary B. A., 1929-1977 (Box 23, Folder 702)
  - Partridge, Elizabeth, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 703)
  - Pearson, Alison, 1966-1974 (Box 23, Folder 704)
  - Pearson, Rodney, 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 705)
  - Perry, Charlotte, 1929-1972 (Box 23, Folder 706)
  - Perry, Edward D., 1930 (Box 23, Folder 707)
  - Phillips, Henry, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 708)
  - Phillips, Margaret F., 1947-1950 (Box 23, Folder 708)
  - Pierson, Laetitia V., 1949-1950, undated (Box 23, Folder 709)
  - Porter, Lois, 1952-1965 (Box 23, Folder 710)
  - Quarrier, Eliza, 1928-1939, undated (Box 23, Folder 711)
  - R, 1929-1980, undated (Box 23, Folder 712)
  - Reimer, Ursula(*), 1924-1961, undated (Box 23, Folder 713-714)
  - Ritchie, Jane, 1972-1978 (Box 23, Folder 715)
  - Roche, James Curtis, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 716)
  - Roche, Louise Coverly, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 716)
  - Roche, Louise Curtis(*), 1929-1978, undated (Box 23, Folder 717)
  - Rollins, Caroline, 1964-1976 (Box 23, Folder 718)
  - Rollins, Margaret, 1937-1970 (Box 23, Folder 719)
  - Rutishauser, Helen, 1963-1974 (Box 23, Folder 720)
  - S, 1924-1978, undated (Box 23, Folder 721)
  - Sharpe, Dorothea, 1954, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 722)
  - Shaw, Katherine Perry, 1931-1939, undated (Box 23, Folder 723)
  - Simonds, Bruce, 1929-1964 (Box 23, Folder 724)
  - Smith, Charles G., Jr., 1931 (Box 23, Folder 725)
  - Sozzani, Emanuela de Dampierre(*), 1961-1979 (Box 23, Folder 726)
  - Steer, Francis W., 1959-1978 (Box 23, Folder 727)
  - Stuart, Hannah, 1973, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 728)
  - Stevens, Eva, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 729)
  - Sullivan, Catherine Ellinwood, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 730)
  - Sullivan, Elizabeth Anne, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 730)
  - Sullivan, Jeanet Loomis, 1922-1932 (Box 23, Folder 731-735)
  - Sullivan, Jeanet Loomis, 1932-1945, undated (Box 24, Folder 736-740)
  - Sullivan, Mary Barrett, 1956-1980 (Box 24, Folder 741)
  - Sullivan, Nancy Alison(*), 1924-1958, undated (Box 24, Folder 742-743)
  - Sullivan, Walter Seager (1866-1949)(*), 1920-1947, undated (Box 24, Folder 744-747)
  - Sullivan, Walter Seager (1918-)(*), 1924-1979, undated (Box 24, Folder 748-751)
  - Sullivan, Theodore Loomis, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 752)
  - Sulzberger, Iphigenie Ochs(*), 1929-1977, undated (Box 24, Folder 753)
  - T, 1922-1976, undated (Box 24, Folder 754)
  - Tempest, Valerie(*), 1951-1976 (Box 24, Folder 755)
  - Thompson, Cecily(*), 1931-1933 (Box 24, Folder 756)
  - Turckheim, Madeline de, 1930-1954 (Box 25, Folder 757)
  - Tyler, Eugenie C.(*), 1938-1972 (Box 25, Folder 758)
  - Tyler, Morris, 1947-1980, undated (Box 25, Folder 759)
  - Tyng, Lila, 1952-1977, undated (Box 25, Folder 760)
  - V, 1945, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 761)
  - W, 1926-1980, undated (Box 25, Folder 762)
  - Wardwell, Edward R., 1958, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 763)
  - Wardwell, Lee, 1956-1959 (Box 25, Folder 764)
  - Wells, Antoinette, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 765)
  - Wells, Dorothy Pomeroy, 1976, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 765)
  - Wells, Mary Pomeroy, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 766)
  - Wells, Pauline Pomeroy, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 766)
  - Wight, Elizabeth, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 767)
  - Willis-Bund, Anne, 1960-1975 (Box 25, Folder 768)
  - Willis-Bund, Frank L. M., 1963-1978 (Box 25, Folder 769)
  - Willis-Bund, Jane, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 770)
  - Withington, Dorothea B., 1949-1958 (Box 25, Folder 771)
  - Woolsey, Jean E., 1929-1950 (Box 25, Folder 772)
  - Y, 1928-1949 (Box 25, Folder 773)
  - Z, 1938, undated (Box 25, Folder 774)
  - Zane, Esther E., 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 775)
  - Unidentified: First names A - P, 1950-1977, undated, 1929-1978, undated, 1926-1979, undated, 1924-1979, undated (Box 25, Folder 776-779)
  - Unidentified: First names R - W, 1922-1980, undated (Box 25, Folder 780)
  - Unidentified relatives, 1929-1961, undated (Box 25, Folder 781)
  - Unidentified Bryn Mawr friends, 1924 (Box 25, Folder 782)
  - Unidentified correspondence, 1923-1977, undated (Box 25, Folder 783)
  - Unfinished letters, 1928, undated (Box 25, Folder 784)
  - Cards and invitations, 1927-1928, undated (Box 25, Folder 785)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1923-1977, undated (Box 25, Folder 786)
- Early Curtis Papers, 1762-1814; Series IV; 8.2 linear feet (20 boxes)
  Series IV contains two sections, Personal Papers and Business Papers. The Personal Papers section contains the letters and other papers of several nineteenth century ancestors of Lewis Perry Curtis. All correspondence is arranged chronologically and it fills Boxes 26-29. Undated correspondence follows dated correspondence, Box 29, folders 857-861. Following the correspondence in Boxes 30-34 are personal files on Curtises and other related individuals. These files are arranged alphabetically by surname and chronologically within each folder. A small amount of miscellaneous material comes after the personal files in Box 34, folders 954-965.
  Business Papers consists of correspondence, subject files, oversize materials, and bound business records. Correspondence arranged chronologically is found in Box 35, folders 966-985, and is immediately followed by subject files, arranged alphabetically by person or subject. Oversize materials are located in Box 41 and are arranged in alphabetical order. Bound business records are in Boxes 42-45.
  - Personal Papers
    - Correspondence, 1797-1802, 1807-1835, 1836 January-Oct, 1837-1841 (Box 26, Folder 787-803)
    - Correspondence, 1842-1866 (Box 27, Folder 804-823)
    - Correspondence, 1867-1891 (Box 28, Folder 824-841)
    - Correspondence, 1892 February-December (Box 28, Folder 842-843)
    - Correspondence, 1893-1894 March-Aug, 1895-1906 (Box 29, Folder 844-852)
    - Correspondence, 1912-1914 (Box 29, Folder 853-856)
    - Correspondence: Family B - W, undated (Box 29, Folder 857)
    - Correspondence: Curtis, Emma Steele, undated (Box 29, Folder 858)
    - Correspondence: Steele, Augusta Perry, undated (Box 29, Folder 859)
    - Correspondence: Friends and unidentified, undated (Box 29, Folder 860)
    - Correspondence: Letter fragments, undated (Box 29, Folder 861)
    - Beers, Andrew: accounts with Joseph D. Beers, 1819 (Box 30, Folder 862)
    - Beers, Andrew: papers, 1797-1828 (Box 30, Folder 863)
      General
      See also: box 41, folders 1081-1083
    - Beers, Jannet Phelps: memorandum, 1858 (Box 30, Folder 864)
    - Beers, Joseph D.: accounts with Elisha Mills, 1845-1858 (Box 30, Folder 865)
    - Beers, Joseph D.: diary, 1851 (Box 30, Folder 866)
    - Beers, Joseph D.: estate, 1863-1885, undated (Box 30, Folder 867)
    - Beers, Joseph D.: estate book, 1864 (Box 30, Folder 868)
    - Beers, Joseph D.: Papers, 1808-1850, undated (Box 30, Folder 869)
    - Beers, Joseph D.: settlement with Sarah Turell Beers, 1859-1892, undated (Box 30, Folder 870)
    - Beers, Joseph D.: wallet (Box 30, Folder 871)
    - Beers, Joseph D.: will, 1863 (Box 30, Folder 872)
    - Beers, Mary Chapman: estate, 1849-1863 (Box 30, Folder 873)
    - Beers, Mary Chapman: papers, 1834 (Box 30, Folder 874)
    - Beers Realty Co., 1913-1914 (Box 30, Folder 875)
    - Beers, Sarah: papers, 1797-1803 (Box 30, Folder 876)
    - Beers, Sarah Turell: receipts, 1864-1894 (Box 30, Folder 877)
    - "The Beers Family" by Alice Curtis Desmond, 1939 (Box 30, Folder 878)
    - Cadwell, Roderick: estate, 1809 (Box 30, Folder 879)
    - Curtis, Agur: papers, 1785-1864,undated (Box 30, Folder 880)
    - Curtis, Agur: will, 1824 (Box 30, Folder 881)
    - Curtis, Benjamin: papers, 1852-1859 (Box 30, Folder 882)
    - Curtis, Benjamin L.: bills, 1900 (Box 30, Folder 883)
    - Curtis, Benjamin L.: calling cards & invitations (Box 30, Folder 884)
    - Curtis, Benjamin L.: Columbia College papers, 1854-1855 (Box 31, Folder 885)
    - Curtis, Benjamin L.: composition, [ca 1853] (Box 31, Folder 886)
    - Curtis, Benjamin L.: day book, 1893 (Box 31, Folder 887)
    - Curtis, Benjamin L.: essay on Latin literature and note on Greece, undated (Box 31, Folder 888)
    - Curtis, Benjamin L.: estate, 1900-1902, undated (Box 31, Folder 889-892)
    - Curtis, Benjamin L.: exercises, undated (Box 31, Folder 893)
    - Curtis, Benjamin L.: Hotel Renaissance papers, 1899-1900 (Box 31, Folder 894)
    - Curtis, Benjamin L.: papers, 1846-1894 (Box 31, Folder 895)
    - Curtis, Benjamin L.: statement on Florida lands, undated (Box 31, Folder 896)
    - Curtis, Benjamin L.: Curtis heirs, 1893 (Box 31, Folder 897)
      See also: box 41, folders 1087-1088
    - Curtis, Emma Steele: book of poems, undated (Box 31, Folder 898)
    - Curtis, Elizabeth Overing, 1840-1883 (Box 32, Folder 899)
    - Curtis, George W. L. vs Benjamin L. Curtis et al, 1891 (Box 32, Folder 900)
    - Curtis, George W. L.: photographs of sons, undated (Box 32, Folder 901)
    - Curtis, Huldah: papers, 1845-1858 (Box 32, Folder 902)
    - Curtis, Joseph D. B.: illness and death, 1868-1870 (Box 32, Folder 903)
    - Curtis, Joseph D. B.: papers, 1839-1851, undated (Box 32, Folder 904)
    - Curtis, Joseph D. B.: remarks, undated (Box 32, Folder 905)
    - Curtis, Lewis: calling cards, undated (Box 32, Folder 906)
    - Curtis, Lewis: death, 1883 (Box 32, Folder 907)
    - Curtis, Lewis: estate, 1883-1896, undated (Box 32, Folder 908-910)
    - Curtis, Lewis: letter book, 1860-1867 (Box 32, Folder 911)
    - Curtis, Lewis: letter book, 1870-1874 (Box 32, Folder 912)
    - Curtis, Lewis: papers, 1828-1882 (Box 32, Folder 913)
    - Curtis, Lewis: residence 4 Bowling Green papers, 1821-1852, undated (Box 32, Folder 914)
    - Curtis, Lewis: trustee, 1842-1843 (Box 32, Folder 915)
      See also: box 41, folders 1089-1092
    - Curtis, Mrs. Lewis: calling cards, undated (Box 32, Folder 916)
    - Curtis, Lewis A.: agreement, 1893 (Box 32, Folder 917)
    - Curtis, Lewis A.: commencement oration, 1858 (Box 32, Folder 918)
    - Curtis, Lewis A.: papers, 1894-1900 (Box 32, Folder 919)
    - Curtis, Lewis B.: school papers, undated (Box 32, Folder 920)
    - Curtis, Lewis B.: scrapbook over 1861 account book, 1884-1888 (Box 33, Folder 921)
    - Curtis, Louisa Wells: bills, receipts, etc., 1894, undated (Box 33, Folder 922)
    - Curtis, Maria: papers, 1841-1863, undated (Box 33, Folder 923)
    - Curtis, Mary Elizabeth Beers: estate, 1844-1852 (Box 33, Folder 924)
    - Curtis, Mary Elizabeth Beers: inventory of estate, 1836 (Box 33, Folder 925)
    - Curtis, Mary Elizabeth Beers: lock of hair, undated (Box 33, Folder 926)
    - Curtis, Mary Elizabeth Beers: papers, 1826-1835 (Box 33, Folder 927)
    - Curtis, Mary Elizabeth Beers: school exercises, 1817 (Box 33, Folder 928)
    - Curtis, Roderick P.: papers, 1893 (Box 33, Folder 929)
    - Curtis, Roderick P.: photographs, 1861-1875 (Box 33, Folder 930)
    - Curtis, Roderick P.: will, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 931)
    - Curtis and related families: clippings, undated (Box 33, Folder 932)
    - Curtis family: agreements, accounts, etc., 1863-1892 (Box 33, Folder 933)
    - Curtis family: pictures, 1886-1887, undated (Box 33, Folder 934)
    - Curtis family: portraits, 1851, undated (Box 33, Folder 935)
    - Giles, William O.: bankruptcy, 1878 (Box 33, Folder 936)
    - Hughes, Louisa Walter Bishop: journal, 1858-1871 (Box 33, Folder 937)
    - Marvine, Archibald R., 1849-1876 (Box 33, Folder 938)
    - Marvine, Archibald R.: "Archie's hair", 1876 (Box 33, Folder 939)
    - Overing, Henry: papers, 1814, 1883 (Box 34, Folder 940)
    - Overing, Mrs.: calling cards, undated (Box 34, Folder 941)
    - [Shaw, Nathaniel, Jr.?]: account books, 1762, 1766 (Box 34, Folder 942)
    - Steele, Augusta Perry: accounts, 1860-1878 (Box 34, Folder 943)
    - Steele, Julia:S.: diary, 1831 (Box 34, Folder 944)
    - Steele, Samuel: deeds, 1814-1816 (Box 34, Folder 945)
    - Talleyrand-Périgord, Charles Maurice: papers, 1867-1876, undated (Box 34, Folder 946)
    - Talleyrand-Périgord, Elizabeth Curtis: papers, 1868, 1873, undated (Box 34, Folder 947)
    - Wells, Charles S.: obituary, 1895 (Box 34, Folder 948)
    - Wells, Edward Livingston: papers, 1859, 1880 (Box 34, Folder 949)
    - Wells, Jane E. Bucklin: diary Part A, 1844-1845 (Box 34, Folder 950)
    - Wells, Jane E. Bucklin: diary Part B, 1844-1845 (Box 34, Folder 951)
    - Wells, Jane E. Bucklin: diary, 1854-1857 (Box 34, Folder 952)
    - Wells, Mary Hughes: invitations, 1886, 1888 (Box 34, Folder 953)
    - Bills, receipts, etc: miscellaneous, 1811-1868, undated (Box 34, Folder 954)
    - Colonial Dames, 1895-1907, undated (Box 34, Folder 955)
    - Daughters of the American Revolution, 1893-1903, undated (Box 34, Folder 956)
    - The Evening Post (Bridgeport), 1889 October 3 (Box 34, Folder 957)
    - Genealogical notes, undated (Box 34, Folder 958)
    - Greenwood cemetery, 1881-1883 (Box 34, Folder 959)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 34, Folder 960)
    - Miscellaneous calling cards (Box 34, Folder 961)
    - Miscellaneous poetry, 1832-1855 (Box 34, Folder 962)
    - Newspaper clippings: miscellaneous, undated (Box 34, Folder 963)
    - Picture of Mr. Lloyd of London, undated (Box 34, Folder 964)
    - Printed works, 1834-1903, undated (Box 34, Folder 965)
  - Business Papers
    - Business correspondence, 1801-1825 (Box 35, Folder 966-967)
    - Business correspondence, 1827-1830 (Box 35, Folder 968)
    - Business correspondence, 1832-1869 January-November (Box 35, Folder 969-979)
    - Business correspondence, 1870-1890 (Box 35, Folder 980-982)
    - Business correspondence, 1895-1902, n.d (Box 35, Folder 983-985)
    - American Land Co. (Michigan), 1840-1871 (Box 35, Folder 986)
      See also: box 41, folder 1080
    - Apalachicola Land Co. (Florida), 1843-1890 (Box 35, Folder 987)
    - Apalachicola Land Co. (Florida): trustees book, 1842-1843 (Box 35, Folder 988)
    - Arkansas lands, 1835 (Box 36, Folder 989)
    - Beers, Andrew: bills, receipts, etc., 1815-1822, undated (Box 36, Folder 990)
    - Beers, Joseph D.: bills, receipts, etc., 1816-1866, undated (Box 36, Folder 991)
    - Beers, Joseph D.: checks, 1862-1863 (Box 36, Folder 992)
    - Bolton, John: will, 1817 (Box 36, Folder 993)
    - Booraem & Co. (Texas lands), 1833-1897, undated (Box 36, Folder 994-1005)
    - Booraem & Co. (Texas lands): notes paid by L. &. B. Curtis, 1837-1840 (Box 36, Folder 1006)
    - Booraem & Co. (Texas lands): deeds, 1838-1893 (Box 36, Folder 1007)
      See also: box 41, folder 1085
    - Chetwood, F. B.: dealings with Joseph D. Beers, 1858-1874 (Box 37, Folder 1008-1014)
    - Chichester lands (Jamaica, L. I.), 1826-1870 (Box 37, Folder 1015-1016)
    - Curtis & Lamb, 1816-1827 (Box 37, Folder 1017)
    - Curtis, Benjamin L.: bills, receipts, etc., 1864-1887, undated (Box 37, Folder 1018)
    - Curtis, Benjamin L.: miscellaneous papers, 1838-1869 (Box 37, Folder 1019)
    - Curtis, Lewis: bills, receipts, etc., 1851-1872 (Box 37, Folder 1020)
    - Curtis, Lewis: miscellaneous papers, 1809-1882, undated (Box 37, Folder 1021)
    - Curtis, Lewis: checks, 1865-1868 (Box 37, Folder 1022)
    - Curtis, Lewis vs J. Wheeler, 1867 (Box 37, Folder 1023)
    - Curtis, Lewis A.: bills, receipts, etc., 1868-1881 (Box 37, Folder 1024)
    - Curtis, Lewis A.: selling orders, 1901 (Box 37, Folder 1025)
    - Eldert lands (Jamaica, L. I.), 1836-1842, undated (Box 37, Folder 1026)
      See also: box 41, folders 1098-99:
    - Elmhurst, Illinois - brochure, undated (Box 37, Folder 1027)
    - Farmers Loan & Trust Co., 1836-1891, undated (Box 37, Folder 1028)
    - 50th and 51st Streets lands, 1836-1869, undated (Box 38, Folder 1029-1032)
      See also: box 41, folder 1094
    - Flatbush lands (King's County, N.Y.), 1836-1847, undated (Box 38, Folder 1033-1036)
    - Florida Peninsula Land Co., 1836 (Box 38, Folder 1037)
    - Florida channel: report, 1899 (Box 38, Folder 1038)
    - Indian Reservation Trust lands, 1843-1870 (Box 38, Folder 1039)
      See also: box 41, folder 1097
    - Indiana and Illinois lands, 1843-1858 (Box 38, Folder 1040)
    - Jones & Curtis, 1809-1813 (Box 38, Folder 1041)
      See also: box 41, folder 1086
    - L. & B. Curtis & Co., 1827-1872 (Box 38, Folder 1042-1048)
    - L. & B. Curtis & Co., 1873-1885, undated (Box 39, Folder 1049-1050)
      See also: box 41, folder 1100
    - Louisville and Portland Canal Co., 1841-1843 (Box 39, Folder 1051)
    - Miller, Giles, and Curtis trustees, 1846-1884 (Box 39, Folder 1052)
    - Miller, Horace: bond, 1863-1868 (Box 39, Folder 1053)
    - Mississippi Union Bank, 1839-1840 (Box 39, Folder 1054)
    - Moffat & Co., 1849-1851 (Box 39, Folder 1055-1057)
    - New York and Mississippi Land Co., 1834-1889, undated (Box 39, Folder 1058-1060)
      See also: box 41, folder 1102
    - North American Trust and Banking Company, 1843 (Box 39, Folder 1061)
    - Pennsylvania lands, 1849-1890, undated (Box 39, Folder 1062-1066)
    - Robinson vs. The New York Dry Dock Co., 1849 (Box 40, Folder 1067)
    - Sherwood, Samuel and Michigan lands, 1832-1869, undated (Box 40, Folder 1068-1076)
      See also: box 41, folder 1103
    - Thomas Wilson & Co.(Mississippi and Florida lands), 1833-1836 (Box 40, Folder 1077)
    - Maps and plans, undated (Box 40, Folder 1078)